# **Ludger Jean Louis**

Rua São Lourenço, 210, São Lourenço, Niterói, RJ

Phone: (21) 98014-6399 / Email: ludgerjeanlouis@gmail.com

Nationality: Haitian, born in Port-au-Prince. Portfolio: https://ludger-portfolio.netlify.app/

Married

#### GOAL

I hold a degree in Systems Analysis from Haiti and pursued Computer Science at UFRJ. With over 5 years of experience in software development, my career has been a journey of embracing exciting challenges that honed my skills in programming languages such as Java, JavaScript, and Angular. I am brimming with enthusiasm to keep contributing to the world of technology and actively seeking thrilling opportunities.

## **EDUCATION**

- Systems Analysis, CFPH, 2004-2007
- Computer Science, UFRJ, 2011 2016.

#### SKILLS

Web Development:

Angular, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript

#### Database:

MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite

Programming Language

Java, Javascript, Php, NodeJs.

Project Management:

Kanban.

## Extra:

 Git, Github, MS-Word, MS-Excel, MS-PowerPoint, Photoshop, Adaptability, Teamwork, Communication, Proactivity, Creativity, Ease of learning

## **LANGUAGES**

English: Intermediate
Portuguese: Fluent

French: Native language

Haitian Creole: Native language

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **UR Company**

FullStack Developer

2021 - 2023

Development of applications using Java, Angular, HTML, CSS.

Implementation of procedures in PostgreSQL for data insertion, updating, and deletion.

# Atrevo Comunicação e Design

Web developer

2015 - 2017

Development of websites using PHP, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Implementation of the layout (developed in Photoshop) using Adobe

Dreamweaver.

Implementation of procedures in MySQL for data insertion, updating, and deletion.

#### Viva Rio

2014 - 2015

# **Host of the InfoTech Program**

InfoTech was a radio program about technology conducted in two languages, Haitian Creole and French. The target audience was Haitians, which explains the choice of both languages. The idea behind InfoTech was to illustrate how today's world is divided between the real and the virtual, showcasing the comprehensive nature of technology.

The program was a success and greatly aided people, specifically the Haitian community, in understanding and mastering various concepts of information technology and communication applied in different fields.

# Mundvs Software e Serviços Ltda.

Web developer

2012 - 2013

Production and sending of Email Marketing.

Implementation of the layout (developed in Photoshop) using Adobe

Dreamweaver.

Implementation of procedures in MySQL for data insertion, updating, and deletion.

## PaketNet - Lanhouse

2006 - 2009

Owner

Technology and business management.

- Network administration
- Router configuration
- Installation of antennas for radio signal reception.
- Peripheral sales and computer maintenance.